<resources>

    <string name="app_name">XYZ Reader</string>
    <string name="welcome_xyz_reader">Welcome to XYZ Reader!</string>

    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>

    <string name="up">Up</string>

    <string name="paragraph">"For starters, let me try to summarize the lessons and intuitions I've had about ebooks from my release of two novels and most of a short story collection online under a Creative Commons license. A parodist who published a list of alternate titles for the presentations at this event called this talk, \"eBooks Suck Right Now,\" [eBooks suck right now] and as funny as that is, I don't think it's true.  No, if I had to come up with another title for this talk, I'd call it: \"Ebooks: You're Soaking in Them.\" [Ebooks: You're Soaking in Them] That's because I think that the shape of ebooks to come is almost visible in the way that people interact with text today, and that the job of authors who want to become rich and famous is to come to a better understanding of that shape.  I haven't come to a perfect understanding. I don't know what the future of the book looks like. But I have ideas, and I'll share them with you:  1. Ebooks aren't marketing. [Ebooks aren't marketing] OK, so ebooks *are* marketing: that is to say that giving away ebooks sells more books. Baen Books, who do a lot of series publishing, have found that giving away electronic editions of the previous installments in their series to coincide with the release of a new volume sells the hell out of the new book -- and the backlist. And the number of people who wrote to me to tell me about how much they dug the ebook and so bought the paper-book far exceeds the number of people who wrote to me and said, \"Ha, ha, you hippie, I read your book for free and now I'm not gonna buy it.\" But ebooks *shouldn't* be just about marketing: ebooks are a goal unto themselves. In the final analysis, more people will read more words off more screens and fewer words off fewer pages and when those two lines cross, ebooks are gonna have to be the way that writers earn their keep, not the way that they promote the dead-tree editions.  2. Ebooks complement paper books. [Ebooks complement paper books]. Having an ebook is good. Having a paper book is good. Having both is even better. One reader wrote to me and said that he read half my first novel from the bound book, and printed the other half on scrap-paper to read at the beach. Students write to me to say that it's easier to do their term papers if they can copy and paste their quotations into their word-processors. Baen readers use the electronic editions of their favorite series to build concordances of characters, places and events.  3. Unless you own the ebook, you don't 0wn the book [Unless you own the ebook, you don't 0wn the book]."</string>

</resources>
